docjar.com 2005-04-03

# DocJar Privacy Statement

[](http://www.docjar.com/) **Application:** DocJar.com, and DocJar Eclipse Plug-In  
**URL:** http://www.docjar.com, http://www.docjar.net, and http://www.docjar.org

DocJar has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this application. 

**Personal Information**  
•This application does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.  
•Since we do not collect any personal information with this application, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

**Information Automatically Logged**  
•This application records the browser type to monitor market penetration of various web browsers so we can better determine the Internet technologies we may utilize in the design of our pages.  
•Our server software logs IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site.  
•This application uses page referrer data - that is, information about the page that linked you to this page - to determine to what extent our page is referenced by other resources on the Web. This data may be used to preserve the integrity of our computingresources.

**Cookies**  
•This application uses cookies for session management. Cookies are only used to improve user experience. We do not save user cookies into our system. 

**Security**  
• This application has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Log file access is restricted to system administrators while stored on the server. Log files are rotated regularly and archived in a secure location.

**Contact Information**  
•If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact admin@docjar.com.  
  
Copyright © 2005, Jax Systems LLC, New Jersey, U.S.A. All rights reserved.
